[
  {
    "movies": {
      "telugu": [
        {
          "question": "Who is the lead actor in 'Baahubali'?",
          "options": ["Prabhas", "Nani", "Allu Arjun", "Ram Charan"],
          "answer": "Prabhas",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress played the lead role in 'Rangasthalam'?",
          "options": [
            "Samantha Ruth Prabhu",
            "Kajal Aggarwal",
            "Anushka Shetty",
            "Shruti Haasan"
          ],
          "answer": "Samantha Ruth Prabhu",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the song 'Vachinde'?",
          "options": [
            "Fidaa",
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Rangasthalam",
            "Jersey"
          ],
          "answer": "Fidaa",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie has the famous song 'Butta Bomma'?",
          "options": ["Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo", "RRR", "Pushpa", "Baahubali"],
          "answer": "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed 'Baahubali'?",
          "options": [
            "S. S. Rajamouli",
            "Trivikram Srinivas",
            "Puri Jagannadh",
            "Chandrasekhar Yeleti"
          ],
          "answer": "S. S. Rajamouli",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the lead role in 'Jersey'?",
          "options": ["Nani", "Suriya", "Vijay Deverakonda", "Ram Charan"],
          "answer": "Nani",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie featured the song 'Samajavaragamana'?",
          "options": [
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Fidaa",
            "Bheeshma",
            "Kshana Kshanam"
          ],
          "answer": "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the lead actress in the movie 'Pelli Sandadi'?",
          "options": [
            "Sree Leela",
            "Rashmika Mandanna",
            "Anushka Shetty",
            "Nithya Menen"
          ],
          "answer": "Sree Leela",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor is known for his role in 'RRR'?",
          "options": [
            "N.T. Rama Rao Jr.",
            "Allu Arjun",
            "Mahesh Babu",
            "Vijay Deverakonda"
          ],
          "answer": "N.T. Rama Rao Jr.",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film won the 2021 Nandi Award for Best Film?",
          "options": ["Kshana Kshanam", "RRR", "Jersey", "Karthikeya 2"],
          "answer": "RRR",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the role of 'Shiva' in 'Baahubali'?",
          "options": [
            "Prabhas",
            "N.T. Rama Rao Jr.",
            "Mahesh Babu",
            "Ram Charan"
          ],
          "answer": "Prabhas",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the film 'Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo'?",
          "options": [
            "Allu Arjun",
            "N.T. Rama Rao Jr.",
            "Vijay Deverakonda",
            "Suriya"
          ],
          "answer": "Allu Arjun",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Rangasthalam'?",
          "options": ["Sukumar", "Rajamouli", "Vamsi Paidipally", "Krish"],
          "answer": "Sukumar",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the lead actress in 'Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo'?",
          "options": [
            "Pooja Hegde",
            "Samantha Ruth Prabhu",
            "Kajal Aggarwal",
            "Rashmika Mandanna"
          ],
          "answer": "Pooja Hegde",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie features the song 'Srivalli'?",
          "options": [
            "Pushpa",
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Baahubali",
            "Rangasthalam"
          ],
          "answer": "Pushpa",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who composed the music for the film 'Fidaa'?",
          "options": [
            "Shakti Kanth Karthick",
            "Devi Sri Prasad",
            "M. M. Keeravani",
            "Thaman S."
          ],
          "answer": "Shakti Kanth Karthick",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Telugu movie won the National Award for Best Feature Film?",
          "options": ["Kshana Kshanam", "Baahubali", "Karthikeya 2", "RRR"],
          "answer": "Baahubali",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie had the famous song 'Pillaa Raa'?",
          "options": [
            "RX 100",
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Geetha Govindam",
            "Sye"
          ],
          "answer": "RX 100",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Sye'?",
          "options": ["Nithiin", "Suriya", "Vijay Deverakonda", "Ram Charan"],
          "answer": "Nithiin",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie had the hit song 'Aarambhame Le'?",
          "options": ["Kshana Kshanam", "Jersey", "Rangasthalam", "Baahubali"],
          "answer": "Jersey",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie directed by S. S. Rajamouli is based on the life of a historical figure?",
          "options": ["Baahubali", "Magadheera", "Eega", "RRR"],
          "answer": "Baahubali",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor won the Nandi Award for Best Actor for his performance in 'Kshana Kshanam'?",
          "options": ["Sumanth", "Venkatesh", "Nani", "Chiranjeevi"],
          "answer": "Sumanth",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "In which movie did Allu Arjun play a character named 'DJ'?",
          "options": [
            "DJ: Duvvada Jagannadham",
            "Pushpa",
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Race Gurram"
          ],
          "answer": "DJ: Duvvada Jagannadham",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the Telugu film 'Baahubali 2: The Conclusion'?",
          "options": [
            "S. S. Rajamouli",
            "Koratala Siva",
            "Trivikram Srinivas",
            "Puri Jagannadh"
          ],
          "answer": "S. S. Rajamouli",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Kshana Kshanam'?",
          "options": [
            "Sumanth",
            "Venkatesh",
            "N.T. Rama Rao Jr.",
            "Chiranjeevi"
          ],
          "answer": "Sumanth",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the composer of the music for the film 'Baahubali'?",
          "options": [
            "M. M. Keeravani",
            "Devi Sri Prasad",
            "Thaman S.",
            "A. R. Rahman"
          ],
          "answer": "M. M. Keeravani",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie features the song 'gutlo vundi bellam mukka'?",
          "options": ["Sye", "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo", "Pushpa", "Fidaa"],
          "answer": "Sye",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Geetha Govindam'?",
          "options": ["Vijay Deverakonda", "Allu Arjun", "Ram Charan", "Nani"],
          "answer": "Vijay Deverakonda",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor played the role of 'Madhuravani' in 'Kshana Kshanam'?",
          "options": ["Rohini", "Anjali", "Kajal Aggarwal", "Brahmanandam"],
          "answer": "Rohini",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film featured the song 'Ramuloo Ramulaa'?",
          "options": [
            "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
            "Fidaa",
            "Sye",
            "Kshana Kshanam"
          ],
          "answer": "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "hindi": [
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Which Bollywood film features the famous song 'Kal Ho Na Ho'?",
          "options": [
            "Kal Ho Na Ho",
            "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
            "Kabhi Khushi Kabhi Gham",
            "Lagaan"
          ],
          "answer": "Kal Ho Na Ho"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who played the lead role in the movie '3 Idiots'?",
          "options": [
            "Aamir Khan",
            "Shah Rukh Khan",
            "Salman Khan",
            "Hrithik Roshan"
          ],
          "answer": "Aamir Khan"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Which Bollywood movie is based on the life of cricketer M.S. Dhoni?",
          "options": [
            "M.S. Dhoni: The Untold Story",
            "Chak De! India",
            "Lagaan",
            "Azhar"
          ],
          "answer": "M.S. Dhoni: The Untold Story"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Which 2015 film starred Ranbir Kapoor and Deepika Padukone?",
          "options": [
            "Tamasha",
            "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani",
            "Bajirao Mastani",
            "Piku"
          ],
          "answer": "Tamasha"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Bollywood'?",
          "options": [
            "Shah Rukh Khan",
            "Amitabh Bachchan",
            "Salman Khan",
            "Ranbir Kapoor"
          ],
          "answer": "Shah Rukh Khan"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Lagaan'?",
          "options": [
            "Ashutosh Gowariker",
            "Rajkumar Hirani",
            "Karan Johar",
            "Sanjay Leela Bhansali"
          ],
          "answer": "Ashutosh Gowariker"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Which actor is known for the iconic role of 'Mogambo'?",
          "options": [
            "Amrish Puri",
            "Shakti Kapoor",
            "Anupam Kher",
            "Prem Chopra"
          ],
          "answer": "Amrish Puri"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who is the lead actress in the movie 'Piku'?",
          "options": [
            "Deepika Padukone",
            "Priyanka Chopra",
            "Kareena Kapoor",
            "Katrina Kaif"
          ],
          "answer": "Deepika Padukone"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who won the Filmfare Award for Best Actor in 2020?",
          "options": [
            "Ranveer Singh",
            "Amitabh Bachchan",
            "Vicky Kaushal",
            "Ayushmann Khurrana"
          ],
          "answer": "Vicky Kaushal"
        },
        {
          "mode": "easy",
          "question": "Who directed 'Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge'?",
          "options": [
            "Aditya Chopra",
            "Karan Johar",
            "Rajkumar Hirani",
            "Sanjay Leela Bhansali"
          ],
          "answer": "Aditya Chopra"
        },
        {
          "mode": "medium",
          "question": "Who played the role of Mary Kom in the 2014 biographical film?",
          "options": [
            "Priyanka Chopra",
            "Deepika Padukone",
            "Kareena Kapoor",
            "Alia Bhatt"
          ],
          "answer": "Priyanka Chopra"
        },
        {
          "mode": "medium",
          "question": "Which actor played the role of 'Bhallaladeva'?",
          "options": ["Rana Daggubati", "Prabhas", "Mahesh Babu", "Ram Charan"],
          "answer": "Rana Daggubati"
        },
        {
          "mode": "medium",
          "question": "Who is the music composer for 'Bajirao Mastani'?",
          "options": [
            "Sanjay Leela Bhansali",
            "A.R. Rahman",
            "Vishal-Shekhar",
            "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy"
          ],
          "answer": "Sanjay Leela Bhansali"
        },
        {
          "mode": "medium",
          "question": "Which film won the 2017 Filmfare Award for Best Director?",
          "options": ["Sultan", "Dangal", "Dear Zindagi", "PK"],
          "answer": "Dangal"
        },
        {
          "mode": "medium",
          "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Kabir Singh'?",
          "options": [
            "Shahid Kapoor",
            "Salman Khan",
            "Hrithik Roshan",
            "Aamir Khan"
          ],
          "answer": "Shahid Kapoor"
        },
        {
          "mode": "hard",
          "question": "Which film won the National Film Award for Best Feature Film in 2017?",
          "options": ["Village Rockstars", "Piku", "Lagaan", "Gully Boy"],
          "answer": "Village Rockstars"
        },
        {
          "mode": "hard",
          "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara'?",
          "options": [
            "Hrithik Roshan",
            "Aamir Khan",
            "Shah Rukh Khan",
            "Salman Khan"
          ],
          "answer": "Hrithik Roshan"
        },
        {
          "mode": "hard",
          "question": "Which movie features the famous dialogue 'Mogambo Khush Hua'?",
          "options": ["Mr. India", "Sholay", "Deewaar", "Dil Se"],
          "answer": "Mr. India"
        },
        {
          "mode": "hard",
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Drishyam'?",
          "options": [
            "Jeethu Joseph",
            "M. Night Shyamalan",
            "Christopher Nolan",
            "S. S. Rajamouli"
          ],
          "answer": "Jeethu Joseph"
        },
        {
          "mode": "hard",
          "question": "Which film's music was composed by Ilaiyaraaja?",
          "options": [
            "Anjali",
            "Sultan",
            "Bajirao Mastani",
            "Kabhi Khushi Kabhi Gham"
          ],
          "answer": "Anjali"
        }
      ],
      "malayalam": [
        {
          "question": "Who played the lead role in the movie 'Drishyam'?",
          "options": [
            "Mohanlal",
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Fahadh Faasil"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohanlal",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie features the popular song 'Entammede Jimikki Kammal'?",
          "options": [
            "Velipadinte Pusthakam",
            "Premam",
            "Bangalore Days",
            "Ustad Hotel"
          ],
          "answer": "Velipadinte Pusthakam",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor played the lead role in 'Premam'?",
          "options": [
            "Nivin Pauly",
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Fahadh Faasil"
          ],
          "answer": "Nivin Pauly",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress starred in 'Manichitrathazhu'?",
          "options": ["Shobhana", "Madhavi", "Meera Jasmine", "Nayantara"],
          "answer": "Shobhana",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which 2017 movie featured the song 'Aaradhike'?",
          "options": [
            "Jacobinte Swargarajyam",
            "Kayal",
            "Angamaly Diaries",
            "Kalyana Samayal Saadham"
          ],
          "answer": "Jacobinte Swargarajyam",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Bangalore Days'?",
          "options": [
            "Anjali Menon",
            "Sidhartha Siva",
            "Lal Jose",
            "Midhun Manuel Thomas"
          ],
          "answer": "Anjali Menon",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Kalyanaraman'?",
          "options": [
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Mohanlal",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Nivin Pauly"
          ],
          "answer": "Dulquer Salmaan",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie had the famous song 'Mazhavil Kavadi'?",
          "options": [
            "Ramji Rao Speaking",
            "Meesa Madhavan",
            "Kilukkam",
            "Godfather"
          ],
          "answer": "Kilukkam",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of 'Ustad Hotel'?",
          "options": ["Anwar Rasheed", "Siddique", "Lal Jose", "Rajesh Pillai"],
          "answer": "Anwar Rasheed",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the role of 'Raghuraman' in 'Kalyanaraman'?",
          "options": [
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Mohanlal",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Nivin Pauly"
          ],
          "answer": "Dulquer Salmaan",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie starred Mohanlal and featured the song 'Aathimannil'?",
          "options": [
            "Kilukkam",
            "Manichitrathazhu",
            "Rajavinte Makan",
            "Meesa Madhavan"
          ],
          "answer": "Kilukkam",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the film 'Drishyam'?",
          "options": [
            "Jeethu Joseph",
            "Rajesh Pillai",
            "Shyamaprasad",
            "B Unnikrishnan"
          ],
          "answer": "Jeethu Joseph",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the character 'Vijayan' played by Mohanlal?",
          "options": [
            "Rajavinte Makan",
            "Manichitrathazhu",
            "Meesa Madhavan",
            "Kilukkam"
          ],
          "answer": "Rajavinte Makan",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie starred Nivin Pauly as the lead and featured the song 'Poomuthole'?",
          "options": [
            "Premam",
            "Jacobinte Swargarajyam",
            "Kalyanaraman",
            "Neram"
          ],
          "answer": "Premam",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Angamaly Diaries'?",
          "options": [
            "Lijo Jose Pellissery",
            "Anjali Menon",
            "Alphonse Puthren",
            "Sidhartha Siva"
          ],
          "answer": "Lijo Jose Pellissery",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Malayalam movie features a memorable performance by Fahadh Faasil as 'Sam'?",
          "options": [
            "Take Off",
            "Maheshinte Prathikaaram",
            "C/O Saira Banu",
            "Vikramadithyan"
          ],
          "answer": "Take Off",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress played the role of 'Sita' in the movie 'Kalyanaraman'?",
          "options": [
            "Nithya Menen",
            "Meera Jasmine",
            "Shobhana",
            "Manju Warrier"
          ],
          "answer": "Nithya Menen",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of 'Premam'?",
          "options": [
            "Alphonse Puthren",
            "Rajesh Pillai",
            "Jeethu Joseph",
            "Lal Jose"
          ],
          "answer": "Alphonse Puthren",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Malayalam film was India’s official entry for the Best Foreign Language Film at the Oscars in 2015?",
          "options": ["Court", "Drishyam", "Lal Kaptaan", "Vikramadithyan"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Ennu Ninte Moideen'?",
          "options": [
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Nivin Pauly",
            "Mohanlal"
          ],
          "answer": "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film is considered to be the first neo-realistic movie in Malayalam?",
          "options": [
            "Satyakam",
            "Kaalal Pada",
            "Adoor Gopalakrishnan’s 'Swayamvaram'",
            "Nritashala"
          ],
          "answer": "Adoor Gopalakrishnan’s 'Swayamvaram'",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which 2019 Malayalam film had the famous line 'Ithinte Pidikatha Aanakkanum Arangottil?'?",
          "options": [
            "Vikramadithyan",
            "Kalyanaraman",
            "Bangalore Days",
            "Kalyana Samayal Saadham"
          ],
          "answer": "Vikramadithyan",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Take Off'?",
          "options": [
            "Mahesh Narayan",
            "Anwar Rasheed",
            "Sidhique",
            "Rajesh Pillai"
          ],
          "answer": "Mahesh Narayan",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Malayalam movie had the character 'Raghuraman'?",
          "options": [
            "Ustad Hotel",
            "Vikramadithyan",
            "Take Off",
            "Oru Vadakkan Selfie"
          ],
          "answer": "Ustad Hotel",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in 'Maheshinte Prathikaaram'?",
          "options": [
            "Fahadh Faasil",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran",
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Mohanlal"
          ],
          "answer": "Fahadh Faasil",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which 2016 film won the Kerala State Film Award for Best Art Director?",
          "options": ["Kammatipaadam", "Kalyanaraman", "Raja Rani", "Take Off"],
          "answer": "Kammatipaadam",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which director is known for his involvement in the modern Malayalam cinema movement?",
          "options": [
            "Lijo Jose Pellissery",
            "Alphonse Puthren",
            "Jeethu Joseph",
            "Sidhique"
          ],
          "answer": "Lijo Jose Pellissery",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which 2018 Malayalam film has been recognized as the best romantic film by the Kerala State Film Awards?",
          "options": [
            "Oru Kuprasidha Payyan",
            "Poomaram",
            "Love Action Drama",
            "Vikramadithyan"
          ],
          "answer": "Oru Kuprasidha Payyan",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the role of the main antagonist in the movie 'Oru Vadakkan Selfie'?",
          "options": [
            "Nivin Pauly",
            "Dulquer Salmaan",
            "Fahadh Faasil",
            "Prithviraj Sukumaran"
          ],
          "answer": "Fahadh Faasil",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film won the Kerala State Film Award for Best Feature Film in 2014?",
          "options": ["Bangalore Days", "Kali", "Premam", "Charlie"],
          "answer": "Charlie",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "bengali": [
        {
          "question": "Who played the lead role in the movie 'Pather Panchali'?",
          "options": [
            "Soumitra Chatterjee",
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Uttam Kumar",
            "Rajesh Sharma"
          ],
          "answer": "Soumitra Chatterjee",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the popular song 'Ei To Bolechhi Kemon'?",
          "options": [
            "Baishe Srabon",
            "Chander Pahar",
            "Satyajit Ray's Feluda Series",
            "Magno Mainak"
          ],
          "answer": "Baishe Srabon",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the famous director of the movie 'Pather Panchali'?",
          "options": [
            "Satyajit Ray",
            "Rituparno Ghosh",
            "Aparna Sen",
            "Tapan Sinha"
          ],
          "answer": "Satyajit Ray",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in 'Chander Pahar'?",
          "options": [
            "Dev",
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Jisshu Sengupta",
            "Rupam Islam"
          ],
          "answer": "Dev",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie featured the song 'Ami Shubhechha Boli'?",
          "options": [
            "Baishe Srabon",
            "Chotushkone",
            "Shwet Patharer Thala",
            "Jaatishwar"
          ],
          "answer": "Baishe Srabon",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali film has the popular song 'Tumi Ase Aso'?",
          "options": [
            "Moner Manush",
            "Jaatishwar",
            "Chhaya-O-Chhobi",
            "Ghare Baire"
          ],
          "answer": "Moner Manush",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the film 'Ghare Baire'?",
          "options": [
            "Satyajit Ray",
            "Rituparno Ghosh",
            "Buddhadeb Dasgupta",
            "Aparna Sen"
          ],
          "answer": "Satyajit Ray",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress played the role of 'Panna' in 'Jaatishwar'?",
          "options": [
            "Jaya Ahsan",
            "Swastika Mukherjee",
            "Koel Mallick",
            "Rituparna Sengupta"
          ],
          "answer": "Jaya Ahsan",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the song 'Dheere Dheere Se'?",
          "options": [
            "Ghare Baire",
            "Moner Manush",
            "Jaatishwar",
            "Chhaya-O-Chhobi"
          ],
          "answer": "Moner Manush",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played the role of 'Feluda' in the Satyajit Ray's series?",
          "options": [
            "Soumitra Chatterjee",
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Amitabh Bachchan",
            "Ranjit Mallick"
          ],
          "answer": "Soumitra Chatterjee",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Baishe Srabon'?",
          "options": [
            "Parambrata Chatterjee",
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Dev",
            "Jisshu Sengupta"
          ],
          "answer": "Parambrata Chatterjee",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed 'Chhaya-O-Chhobi'?",
          "options": [
            "Rituparno Ghosh",
            "Satyajit Ray",
            "Aparna Sen",
            "Tapan Sinha"
          ],
          "answer": "Rituparno Ghosh",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali actor is known for his role in 'Jaatishwar'?",
          "options": [
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Dev",
            "Soham Chakraborty",
            "Rupam Islam"
          ],
          "answer": "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who composed the music for the movie 'Moner Manush'?",
          "options": [
            "Kabir Suman",
            "Shantanu Moitra",
            "Anupam Roy",
            "Arijit Singh"
          ],
          "answer": "Kabir Suman",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film directed by Rituparno Ghosh won the National Film Award for Best Feature Film?",
          "options": [
            "Chhaya-O-Chhobi",
            "Unishe April",
            "Dahan",
            "Chokher Bali"
          ],
          "answer": "Unishe April",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the movie 'Chander Pahar'?",
          "options": [
            "Buddhadeb Dasgupta",
            "Aniruddha Roy Chowdhury",
            "Kamaleshwar Mukherjee",
            "Srijit Mukherji"
          ],
          "answer": "Kamaleshwar Mukherjee",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the song 'Aar Kothao Kothao'?",
          "options": ["Jaatishwar", "Baishe Srabon", "Dahan", "Mahanagar"],
          "answer": "Jaatishwar",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress starred in 'Chokher Bali'?",
          "options": [
            "Rani Mukerji",
            "Swastika Mukherjee",
            "Konkona Sen Sharma",
            "Sharmila Tagore"
          ],
          "answer": "Rani Mukerji",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali actor won the National Award for Best Actor for his role in 'Baishe Srabon'?",
          "options": [
            "Parambrata Chatterjee",
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Jisshu Sengupta",
            "Rupam Islam"
          ],
          "answer": "Parambrata Chatterjee",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who composed the soundtrack for 'Moner Manush'?",
          "options": [
            "Kabir Suman",
            "Anupam Roy",
            "Shantanu Moitra",
            "Arijit Singh"
          ],
          "answer": "Kabir Suman",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali film won the Golden Lotus Award (Swarna Kamal) at the 2003 National Film Awards?",
          "options": [
            "Chokher Bali",
            "Moner Manush",
            "Ghare Baire",
            "Satyajit Ray's Pather Panchali"
          ],
          "answer": "Ghare Baire",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is known for his role in the movie 'Chhaya-O-Chhobi'?",
          "options": [
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Mithun Chakraborty",
            "Dev",
            "Jisshu Sengupta"
          ],
          "answer": "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali film was selected as India's official entry for the Best Foreign Language Film category at the Oscars in 1997?",
          "options": [
            "The Cloud-Capped Star",
            "Pather Panchali",
            "Aparajito",
            "Ghare Baire"
          ],
          "answer": "The Cloud-Capped Star",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of 'Chokher Bali'?",
          "options": [
            "Rituparno Ghosh",
            "Aparna Sen",
            "Buddhadeb Dasgupta",
            "Satyajit Ray"
          ],
          "answer": "Rituparno Ghosh",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali film won the Filmfare Award for Best Film – East in 2012?",
          "options": [
            "Chhaya-O-Chhobi",
            "Baishe Srabon",
            "Jaatishwar",
            "Shwet Patharer Thala"
          ],
          "answer": "Jaatishwar",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film features the song 'Jodi Tor Dak Shune'?",
          "options": [
            "Moner Manush",
            "Chokher Bali",
            "Ghare Baire",
            "Baishe Srabon"
          ],
          "answer": "Moner Manush",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which director is known for his contributions to Bengali cinema with films like 'Ghare Baire' and 'Aparajito'?",
          "options": [
            "Satyajit Ray",
            "Tapan Sinha",
            "Rituparno Ghosh",
            "Aparna Sen"
          ],
          "answer": "Satyajit Ray",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress starred in the movie 'Chhaya-O-Chhobi'?",
          "options": [
            "Rani Mukerji",
            "Swastika Mukherjee",
            "Koel Mallick",
            "Tanuja"
          ],
          "answer": "Swastika Mukherjee",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor played the role of 'Raghu' in 'Moner Manush'?",
          "options": [
            "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
            "Soham Chakraborty",
            "Mithun Chakraborty",
            "Bipasha Basu"
          ],
          "answer": "Prosenjit Chatterjee",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Bengali film was nominated for the Best Foreign Language Film at the Academy Awards in 1981?",
          "options": [
            "Pather Panchali",
            "The Cloud-Capped Star",
            "Aparajito",
            "Shwet Patharer Thala"
          ],
          "answer": "Pather Panchali",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "marathi": [
        {
          "question": "Who played the lead role in the movie 'Swaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Mohan Agashe",
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Lalit Prabhakar"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohan Agashe",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film won the National Film Award for Best Feature Film in 2015?",
          "options": ["Court", "Court", "Swaas", "Killa"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of the Marathi film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Chaitanya Tamhane",
            "Nagraj Manjule",
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Viju Mane"
          ],
          "answer": "Chaitanya Tamhane",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie features the song 'Apsara Aali'?",
          "options": ["Natarang", "Dholki", "Swaas", "Shwaas"],
          "answer": "Natarang",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who starred as 'Langda Tyagi' in the Marathi movie 'Swaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Shubha Khote",
            "Vijay Jadhav"
          ],
          "answer": "Makarand Deshpande",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi actor is famous for his role in 'Shwaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Vijay Jadhav",
            "Anant Mahadevan",
            "Urmila Matondkar"
          ],
          "answer": "Makarand Deshpande",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of the film 'Swaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Sanjay Leela Bhansali",
            "Nagraj Manjule",
            "Nitin Desai",
            "Ravi Jadhav"
          ],
          "answer": "Nagraj Manjule",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who composed the soundtrack of the movie 'Swaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Ajay Atul",
            "Lalit Pandit",
            "Bappa Lahiri",
            "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy"
          ],
          "answer": "Ajay Atul",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie featured the song 'Kombdi Palali'?",
          "options": ["Natarang", "Killa", "Dholki", "Court"],
          "answer": "Natarang",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress starred in 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Geetanjali Thapa",
            "Urmila Matondkar",
            "Rekha",
            "Shubha Khote"
          ],
          "answer": "Geetanjali Thapa",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor played the lead role in the Marathi film 'Killa'?",
          "options": ["Archit", "Ajinkya", "Ashok Saraf", "Nana Patekar"],
          "answer": "Ajinkya",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the Marathi movie 'Swaas'?",
          "options": [
            "Chaitanya Tamhane",
            "Nagraj Manjule",
            "Ravi Jadhav",
            "Shantanu Roy Choudhury"
          ],
          "answer": "Nagraj Manjule",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who starred in the film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Vijay Jadhav",
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Anant Mahadevan",
            "Geetanjali Thapa"
          ],
          "answer": "Geetanjali Thapa",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie has the famous song 'Madhavi Latha'?",
          "options": ["Swaas", "Dholki", "Natarang", "Swaas"],
          "answer": "Swaas",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who directed the Marathi film 'Natarang'?",
          "options": [
            "Nagraj Manjule",
            "Raj Thackeray",
            "Viju Mane",
            "Ravi Jadhav"
          ],
          "answer": "Ravi Jadhav",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi film featured a popular song 'Kombdi Palali'?",
          "options": ["Natarang", "Court", "Shwaas", "Dholki"],
          "answer": "Natarang",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor starred in the film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Vijay Jadhav",
            "Rajendra Gupta",
            "Raj Thackeray",
            "Anant Mahadevan"
          ],
          "answer": "Rajendra Gupta",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi actor has won the Filmfare Award for Best Actor in a leading role?",
          "options": [
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Vijay Jadhav",
            "Rajendra Gupta",
            "Ajinkya"
          ],
          "answer": "Nana Patekar",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actress starred in 'Court'?",
          "options": ["Geetanjali Thapa", "Shubha Khote", "Madhavi", "Rani"],
          "answer": "Geetanjali Thapa",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who won the National Award for Best Actor for the movie 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Rajendra Gupta",
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Anant Mahadevan"
          ],
          "answer": "Rajendra Gupta",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie has won the National Award for Best Feature Film?",
          "options": ["Court", "Natarang", "Swaas", "Shwaas"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie won the National Film Award for Best Film in 2017?",
          "options": ["Swaas", "Court", "Dholki", "Natarang"],
          "answer": "Swaas",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of the film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Chaitanya Tamhane",
            "Nagraj Manjule",
            "Ravi Jadhav",
            "Viju Mane"
          ],
          "answer": "Chaitanya Tamhane",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi movie had the famous song 'Shwaas'?",
          "options": ["Swaas", "Dholki", "Killa", "Natarang"],
          "answer": "Swaas",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi film won the Best Marathi Film award at the 2016 National Film Awards?",
          "options": ["Court", "Natarang", "Swaas", "Killa"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which actor was awarded the Best Actor award at the 2015 National Film Awards for the Marathi film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Rajendra Gupta",
            "Makarand Deshpande",
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Anant Mahadevan"
          ],
          "answer": "Rajendra Gupta",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi film won the Golden Lotus at the 2017 National Film Awards?",
          "options": ["Court", "Killa", "Swaas", "Swaas"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie won the Best Marathi Film award at the 2014 National Film Awards?",
          "options": ["Court", "Swaas", "Dholki", "Natarang"],
          "answer": "Court",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which film won the National Award for Best Feature Film in 2017?",
          "options": ["Swaas", "Court", "Dholki", "Natarang"],
          "answer": "Swaas",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marathi actor starred in the film 'Court'?",
          "options": [
            "Rajendra Gupta",
            "Anant Mahadevan",
            "Nana Patekar",
            "Makarand Deshpande"
          ],
          "answer": "Rajendra Gupta",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "marvel": [
        {
          "question": "Who played Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
          "options": [
            "Chris Hemsworth",
            "Robert Downey Jr.",
            "Chris Evans",
            "Tom Hiddleston"
          ],
          "answer": "Robert Downey Jr.",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Thor's hammer?",
          "options": ["Mjolnir", "Stormbreaker", "Excalibur", "Thunderstrike"],
          "answer": "Mjolnir",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marvel superhero is known as the 'First Avenger'?",
          "options": ["Iron Man", "Hawkeye", "Captain America", "Thor"],
          "answer": "Captain America",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which movie features the character 'Black Panther'?",
          "options": [
            "Iron Man",
            "Black Panther",
            "Captain America: Civil War",
            "Guardians of the Galaxy"
          ],
          "answer": "Black Panther",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the villain in the movie 'Avengers: Infinity War'?",
          "options": ["Ultron", "Loki", "Thanos", "Hela"],
          "answer": "Thanos",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the real name of Black Widow?",
          "options": [
            "Natasha Romanoff",
            "Wanda Maximoff",
            "Peggy Carter",
            "Sharon Carter"
          ],
          "answer": "Natasha Romanoff",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which character says the phrase 'I am Groot'?",
          "options": ["Rocket Raccoon", "Star-Lord", "Groot", "Gamora"],
          "answer": "Groot",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Avenger was not present in 'Avengers: Age of Ultron'?",
          "options": ["Captain America", "Black Widow", "Hawkeye", "Ant-Man"],
          "answer": "Ant-Man",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who played Spider-Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
          "options": [
            "Andrew Garfield",
            "Tobey Maguire",
            "Tom Holland",
            "Chris Hemsworth"
          ],
          "answer": "Tom Holland",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the organization that Nick Fury works for?",
          "options": ["S.H.I.E.L.D.", "Hydra", "The Avengers", "The X-Men"],
          "answer": "S.H.I.E.L.D.",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the director of the Marvel movie 'Guardians of the Galaxy'?",
          "options": [
            "James Gunn",
            "Jon Favreau",
            "Joss Whedon",
            "Russo Brothers"
          ],
          "answer": "James Gunn",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "In which movie did the character 'Vision' first appear?",
          "options": [
            "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
            "Avengers: Endgame",
            "Captain America: Civil War",
            "Thor: Ragnarok"
          ],
          "answer": "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the father of Thor and Loki?",
          "options": ["Hela", "Odin", "Laufey", "Thanos"],
          "answer": "Odin",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Tony Stark's AI assistant?",
          "options": ["F.R.I.D.A.Y.", "J.A.R.V.I.S.", "Ultron", "Friday"],
          "answer": "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Captain America's shield?",
          "options": [
            "Vibranium Shield",
            "Titanium Shield",
            "Iron Shield",
            "Adamanium Shield"
          ],
          "answer": "Vibranium Shield",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who plays the character of Doctor Strange?",
          "options": [
            "Benedict Cumberbatch",
            "Chris Hemsworth",
            "Chris Evans",
            "Tom Hiddleston"
          ],
          "answer": "Benedict Cumberbatch",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the first villain of the Avengers?",
          "options": ["Loki", "Ultron", "Hela", "Thanos"],
          "answer": "Loki",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which character is portrayed by Scarlett Johansson?",
          "options": [
            "Gamora",
            "Black Widow",
            "Wanda Maximoff",
            "Peggy Carter"
          ],
          "answer": "Black Widow",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which superhero was part of the 'Civil War' in the MCU?",
          "options": [
            "Iron Man",
            "Spider-Man",
            "Black Panther",
            "All of the above"
          ],
          "answer": "All of the above",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "What was the name of the Black Panther's home country?",
          "options": ["Wakanda", "Kamar-Taj", "Sakaar", "Vormir"],
          "answer": "Wakanda",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the villain in 'Thor: The Dark World'?",
          "options": ["Hela", "Ultron", "Malekith", "Loki"],
          "answer": "Malekith",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Infinity Stone was located on Vormir?",
          "options": ["Time Stone", "Space Stone", "Soul Stone", "Mind Stone"],
          "answer": "Soul Stone",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the real name of 'The Winter Soldier'?",
          "options": [
            "Steve Rogers",
            "Bucky Barnes",
            "Sam Wilson",
            "James Rhodes"
          ],
          "answer": "Bucky Barnes",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Marvel movie features the character 'Shang-Chi'?",
          "options": [
            "Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings",
            "Doctor Strange",
            "Thor: Ragnarok",
            "Black Panther"
          ],
          "answer": "Shang-Chi and the Legend of the Ten Rings",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "In which movie does Captain America say, 'Avengers Assemble'?",
          "options": [
            "Avengers: Endgame",
            "Avengers: Age of Ultron",
            "Captain America: Civil War",
            "Avengers: Infinity War"
          ],
          "answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the actor who plays 'Thanos'?",
          "options": [
            "Josh Brolin",
            "Mark Ruffalo",
            "Chris Hemsworth",
            "Chris Evans"
          ],
          "answer": "Josh Brolin",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the spaceship used by the Guardians of the Galaxy?",
          "options": [
            "Star Destroyer",
            "Milano",
            "Ant-Man",
            "Avengers Quinjet"
          ],
          "answer": "Milano",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which superhero’s real name is Wanda Maximoff?",
          "options": ["Scarlet Witch", "Black Widow", "Gamora", "Storm"],
          "answer": "Scarlet Witch",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the ruler of the planet Xandar?",
          "options": ["The Collector", "Yondu", "Nova Prime", "Thanos"],
          "answer": "Nova Prime",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the first superhero to appear in the MCU?",
          "options": ["Iron Man", "The Hulk", "Thor", "Captain America"],
          "answer": "Iron Man",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ]
    },
    "sports": {
      "cricket": [
        {
          "question": "Who is known as the 'Master Blaster' in cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Ricky Ponting",
            "Brian Lara",
            "Virat Kohli"
          ],
          "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the maximum number of overs in a T20 match?",
          "options": ["10", "20", "50", "100"],
          "answer": "20",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country won the ICC Cricket World Cup 2019?",
          "options": ["India", "Australia", "England", "New Zealand"],
          "answer": "England",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which bowler is famous for the 'Doosra' delivery?",
          "options": [
            "Shane Warne",
            "Muttiah Muralitharan",
            "Saqlain Mushtaq",
            "Harbhajan Singh"
          ],
          "answer": "Saqlain Mushtaq",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer is known as 'The Wall'?",
          "options": [
            "Rahul Dravid",
            "Virender Sehwag",
            "MS Dhoni",
            "Kumar Sangakkara"
          ],
          "answer": "Rahul Dravid",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the full form of IPL?",
          "options": [
            "Indian Premier League",
            "International Premier League",
            "Indian Players League",
            "International Players League"
          ],
          "answer": "Indian Premier League",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer has scored the most runs in ODIs?",
          "options": [
            "Ricky Ponting",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Shane Watson"
          ],
          "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "In cricket, how many runs is a 'no ball' worth?",
          "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
          "answer": "1",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country invented the game of cricket?",
          "options": ["India", "Australia", "England", "South Africa"],
          "answer": "England",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is a duck in cricket?",
          "options": [
            "When a player gets out for 0 runs",
            "A ball delivery",
            "When a player scores 100",
            "When a player gets out on the first ball"
          ],
          "answer": "When a player gets out for 0 runs",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who holds the record for the fastest century in ODI cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Shahid Afridi",
            "AB de Villiers",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Martin Guptill"
          ],
          "answer": "AB de Villiers",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which team has won the most ICC T20 World Cups?",
          "options": ["India", "Pakistan", "Australia", "West Indies"],
          "answer": "West Indies",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the highest wicket-taker in Test cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Muttiah Muralitharan",
            "Shane Warne",
            "Anil Kumble",
            "Ravi Ashwin"
          ],
          "answer": "Muttiah Muralitharan",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer was known as 'The Little Master'?",
          "options": [
            "Sunil Gavaskar",
            "Shane Warne",
            "Javed Miandad",
            "Kapil Dev"
          ],
          "answer": "Sunil Gavaskar",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country did MS Dhoni lead to their first T20 World Cup victory?",
          "options": ["India", "Sri Lanka", "Pakistan", "Bangladesh"],
          "answer": "India",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "In cricket, what is the term for a delivery that bounces twice?",
          "options": ["Full toss", "Short ball", "No ball", "Double bounce"],
          "answer": "Double bounce",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who hit the fastest century in T20 cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Shahid Afridi",
            "Chris Gayle",
            "AB de Villiers",
            "David Miller"
          ],
          "answer": "Chris Gayle",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the cricket ground located in Melbourne, Australia?",
          "options": ["Old Trafford", "Eden Gardens", "MCG", "Lord's"],
          "answer": "MCG",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer is known for his helicopter shot?",
          "options": [
            "MS Dhoni",
            "Ricky Ponting",
            "Virender Sehwag",
            "Yuvraj Singh"
          ],
          "answer": "MS Dhoni",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer is called the 'King of Spin'?",
          "options": [
            "Shane Warne",
            "Muttiah Muralitharan",
            "Anil Kumble",
            "Ravichandran Ashwin"
          ],
          "answer": "Muttiah Muralitharan",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who has the highest batting average in Test cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Don Bradman",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Jacques Kallis"
          ],
          "answer": "Don Bradman",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer scored the most runs in a single Test match?",
          "options": [
            "Brian Lara",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Ricky Ponting",
            "Mark Waugh"
          ],
          "answer": "Brian Lara",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which cricketer holds the record for most runs in a calendar year in ODI cricket?",
          "options": [
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Chris Gayle",
            "AB de Villiers"
          ],
          "answer": "Virat Kohli",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the youngest cricketer to score a century in the World Cup?",
          "options": [
            "Shubman Gill",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Joe Root",
            "Ricky Ponting"
          ],
          "answer": "Shubman Gill",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "What was the first-ever country to host a World Cup?",
          "options": ["India", "England", "Australia", "South Africa"],
          "answer": "England",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who holds the record for the most wickets in T20 internationals?",
          "options": [
            "Shakib Al Hasan",
            "Lasith Malinga",
            "Dwayne Bravo",
            "Rashid Khan"
          ],
          "answer": "Lasith Malinga",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the captain of the Indian cricket team before MS Dhoni?",
          "options": [
            "Sourav Ganguly",
            "Kapil Dev",
            "Anil Kumble",
            "Sachin Tendulkar"
          ],
          "answer": "Sourav Ganguly",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "What was the fastest delivery bowled in cricket history?",
          "options": ["161.3 km/h", "155.4 km/h", "153.5 km/h", "149.5 km/h"],
          "answer": "161.3 km/h",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which Indian cricketer is famous for his 'dilscoop' shot?",
          "options": [
            "Yuvraj Singh",
            "MS Dhoni",
            "Suresh Raina",
            "Shikhar Dhawan"
          ],
          "answer": "MS Dhoni",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which bowler is known for the 'Chin Music'?",
          "options": [
            "Shane Warne",
            "Brett Lee",
            "Wasim Akram",
            "Shoaib Akhtar"
          ],
          "answer": "Brett Lee",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "football": [
        {
          "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup 2018?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "France", "Argentina"],
          "answer": "France",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Football'?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Pelé",
            "Diego Maradona"
          ],
          "answer": "Pelé",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer is known for his 'Ronaldo Chop' move?",
          "options": [
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Neymar",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Zlatan Ibrahimović"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club is known as 'The Red Devils'?",
          "options": ["Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
          "answer": "Manchester United",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer holds the record for the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
          "options": [
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Ronaldinho",
            "Zlatan Ibrahimović"
          ],
          "answer": "Lionel Messi",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country is the home of the famous footballer Cristiano Ronaldo?",
          "options": ["Spain", "Portugal", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
          "answer": "Portugal",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of the English Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Wayne Rooney",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Sergio Agüero",
            "Thierry Henry"
          ],
          "answer": "Wayne Rooney",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which team won the UEFA Champions League in 2020?",
          "options": ["Barcelona", "Bayern Munich", "Real Madrid", "Liverpool"],
          "answer": "Bayern Munich",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country is the birthplace of football legend Diego Maradona?",
          "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
          "answer": "Argentina",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cup titles?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Argentina", "Italy"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country hosted the 2014 FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "South Africa", "Germany", "Russia"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer holds the record for the most goals in a single calendar year?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Gerd Müller",
            "Neymar"
          ],
          "answer": "Lionel Messi",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club is known as 'Los Blancos'?",
          "options": [
            "Barcelona",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Atletico Madrid",
            "Valencia"
          ],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of the FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Pele", "Ronaldo Nazário", "Marta", "Miroslav Klose"],
          "answer": "Miroslav Klose",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the first player to win 5 Ballon d'Or titles?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Michel Platini",
            "Zinedine Zidane"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
          "options": ["AC Milan", "Liverpool", "Barcelona", "Real Madrid"],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is known as 'The Egyptian King' in football?",
          "options": [
            "Mohamed Salah",
            "Trezeguet",
            "Mahmoud Hassan",
            "Ahmed Fathi"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohamed Salah",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country won the Euro 2016 tournament?",
          "options": ["Spain", "Portugal", "Germany", "France"],
          "answer": "Portugal",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who won the Golden Boot in the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Harry Kane",
            "Kylian Mbappé",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo"
          ],
          "answer": "Harry Kane",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which player is known as 'The Pharaoh' in football?",
          "options": [
            "Mohamed Salah",
            "Sadio Mane",
            "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
            "Neymar"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohamed Salah",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer scored the fastest goal in the history of the Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Sergio Agüero",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Shane Long",
            "Wayne Rooney"
          ],
          "answer": "Shane Long",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country was the first to win the FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
          "answer": "Uruguay",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the manager of the England national team during the 1966 World Cup victory?",
          "options": [
            "Alf Ramsey",
            "Bobby Robson",
            "Harry Redknapp",
            "Gareth Southgate"
          ],
          "answer": "Alf Ramsey",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the only footballer to have won the Ballon d'Or and the World Cup in the same year?",
          "options": [
            "Ronaldinho",
            "Zinedine Zidane",
            "Kaká",
            "Ronaldo Nazário"
          ],
          "answer": "Ronaldo Nazário",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Raúl",
            "Karim Benzema"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who holds the record for the most appearances in the Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Ryan Giggs",
            "Frank Lampard",
            "Steven Gerrard",
            "Gareth Barry"
          ],
          "answer": "Gareth Barry",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which club did Cristiano Ronaldo join after leaving Manchester United in 2009?",
          "options": [
            "Juventus",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Chelsea",
            "Paris Saint-Germain"
          ],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country has hosted the most FIFA World Cup tournaments?",
          "options": ["Italy", "Brazil", "Germany", "Mexico"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the first African player to win the Ballon d'Or?",
          "options": [
            "George Weah",
            "Didier Drogba",
            "Samuel Eto'o",
            "Jay-Jay Okocha"
          ],
          "answer": "George Weah",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which player has the most international goals in football history?",
          "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ali Daei", "Marta", "Lionel Messi"],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ],
      "olympics": [
        {
          "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup 2018?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "France", "Argentina"],
          "answer": "France",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Football'?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Pelé",
            "Diego Maradona"
          ],
          "answer": "Pelé",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer is known for his 'Ronaldo Chop' move?",
          "options": [
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Neymar",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Zlatan Ibrahimović"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club is known as 'The Red Devils'?",
          "options": ["Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
          "answer": "Manchester United",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer holds the record for the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
          "options": [
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Ronaldinho",
            "Zlatan Ibrahimović"
          ],
          "answer": "Lionel Messi",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country is the home of the famous footballer Cristiano Ronaldo?",
          "options": ["Spain", "Portugal", "Argentina", "Brazil"],
          "answer": "Portugal",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of the English Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Wayne Rooney",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Sergio Agüero",
            "Thierry Henry"
          ],
          "answer": "Wayne Rooney",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which team won the UEFA Champions League in 2020?",
          "options": ["Barcelona", "Bayern Munich", "Real Madrid", "Liverpool"],
          "answer": "Bayern Munich",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country is the birthplace of football legend Diego Maradona?",
          "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
          "answer": "Argentina",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cup titles?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Argentina", "Italy"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "easy"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country hosted the 2014 FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Brazil", "South Africa", "Germany", "Russia"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer holds the record for the most goals in a single calendar year?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Gerd Müller",
            "Neymar"
          ],
          "answer": "Lionel Messi",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club is known as 'Los Blancos'?",
          "options": [
            "Barcelona",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Atletico Madrid",
            "Valencia"
          ],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of the FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Pele", "Ronaldo Nazário", "Marta", "Miroslav Klose"],
          "answer": "Miroslav Klose",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the first player to win 5 Ballon d'Or titles?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Michel Platini",
            "Zinedine Zidane"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which football club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
          "options": ["AC Milan", "Liverpool", "Barcelona", "Real Madrid"],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is known as 'The Egyptian King' in football?",
          "options": [
            "Mohamed Salah",
            "Trezeguet",
            "Mahmoud Hassan",
            "Ahmed Fathi"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohamed Salah",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country won the Euro 2016 tournament?",
          "options": ["Spain", "Portugal", "Germany", "France"],
          "answer": "Portugal",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who won the Golden Boot in the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Harry Kane",
            "Kylian Mbappé",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo"
          ],
          "answer": "Harry Kane",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which player is known as 'The Pharaoh' in football?",
          "options": [
            "Mohamed Salah",
            "Sadio Mane",
            "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
            "Neymar"
          ],
          "answer": "Mohamed Salah",
          "mode": "medium"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which footballer scored the fastest goal in the history of the Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Sergio Agüero",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Shane Long",
            "Wayne Rooney"
          ],
          "answer": "Shane Long",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country was the first to win the FIFA World Cup?",
          "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
          "answer": "Uruguay",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the manager of the England national team during the 1966 World Cup victory?",
          "options": [
            "Alf Ramsey",
            "Bobby Robson",
            "Harry Redknapp",
            "Gareth Southgate"
          ],
          "answer": "Alf Ramsey",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the only footballer to have won the Ballon d'Or and the World Cup in the same year?",
          "options": [
            "Ronaldinho",
            "Zinedine Zidane",
            "Kaká",
            "Ronaldo Nazário"
          ],
          "answer": "Ronaldo Nazário",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
          "options": [
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Raúl",
            "Karim Benzema"
          ],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who holds the record for the most appearances in the Premier League?",
          "options": [
            "Ryan Giggs",
            "Frank Lampard",
            "Steven Gerrard",
            "Gareth Barry"
          ],
          "answer": "Gareth Barry",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which club did Cristiano Ronaldo join after leaving Manchester United in 2009?",
          "options": [
            "Juventus",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Chelsea",
            "Paris Saint-Germain"
          ],
          "answer": "Real Madrid",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which country has hosted the most FIFA World Cup tournaments?",
          "options": ["Italy", "Brazil", "Germany", "Mexico"],
          "answer": "Brazil",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who was the first African player to win the Ballon d'Or?",
          "options": [
            "George Weah",
            "Didier Drogba",
            "Samuel Eto'o",
            "Jay-Jay Okocha"
          ],
          "answer": "George Weah",
          "mode": "hard"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which player has the most international goals in football history?",
          "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Ali Daei", "Marta", "Lionel Messi"],
          "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
          "mode": "hard"
        }
      ]
    },
    "javascript": [
      {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["var", "let", "const", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the value of an uninitialized variable in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["null", "undefined", "0", "NaN"],
        "answer": "undefined",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a function in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
          "function myFunction()",
          "function = myFunction()",
          "let myFunction()",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "function myFunction()",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of '5' + 5 in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["10", "55", "Error", "undefined"],
        "answer": "55",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these is a loop structure in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["for", "while", "do...while", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for an if statement?",
        "options": [
          "if (condition) {}",
          "if {condition} {}",
          "if (condition); {}",
          "if condition {}"
        ],
        "answer": "if (condition) {}",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?",
        "options": ["=", "==", "===", "=>"],
        "answer": "=",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct way to check if a variable is an array?",
        "options": [
          "Array.isArray(variable)",
          "variable.isArray()",
          "typeof variable === 'array'",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Array.isArray(variable)",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you write an infinite loop?",
        "options": [
          "while(true) {}",
          "for(;;) {}",
          "while(1) {}",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to define a constant?",
        "options": ["const", "let", "var", "constant"],
        "answer": "const",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following methods adds an element to the end of an array?",
        "options": ["push()", "pop()", "shift()", "unshift()"],
        "answer": "push()",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the method used to remove the last element from an array?",
        "options": ["pop()", "shift()", "push()", "unshift()"],
        "answer": "pop()",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to add an element to the start of an array?",
        "options": ["push()", "pop()", "shift()", "unshift()"],
        "answer": "unshift()",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you create a new object in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
          "{}",
          "new Object()",
          "Object.create()",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these is used to convert a string into a number?",
        "options": [
          "Number('5')",
          "parseInt('5')",
          "parseFloat('5')",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to remove the first element from an array?",
        "options": ["shift()", "pop()", "push()", "unshift()"],
        "answer": "shift()",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following methods converts a string to uppercase?",
        "options": [
          "toUpperCase()",
          "toLowerCase()",
          "toString()",
          "toFixed()"
        ],
        "answer": "toUpperCase()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'push()' method do in an array?",
        "options": [
          "Adds an element to the end",
          "Adds an element to the start",
          "Removes the first element",
          "Removes the last element"
        ],
        "answer": "Adds an element to the end",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to find the index of a value in an array?",
        "options": ["indexOf()", "find()", "search()", "locate()"],
        "answer": "indexOf()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following methods will return the length of a string?",
        "options": ["length", "size", "count", "length()"],
        "answer": "length",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you convert a string into an array?",
        "options": ["split()", "slice()", "join()", "array()"],
        "answer": "split()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to merge two or more arrays?",
        "options": ["concat()", "join()", "merge()", "combine()"],
        "answer": "concat()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'slice()' method do to an array?",
        "options": [
          "Adds a new element",
          "Removes an element",
          "Returns a shallow copy of a part of an array",
          "Reverses the array"
        ],
        "answer": "Returns a shallow copy of a part of an array",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to join an array into a string?",
        "options": ["join()", "concat()", "slice()", "push()"],
        "answer": "join()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following methods removes the last element from an array?",
        "options": ["pop()", "shift()", "unshift()", "push()"],
        "answer": "pop()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these methods is used to check if an object has a certain property?",
        "options": ["hasOwnProperty()", "include()", "in", "propertyExists()"],
        "answer": "hasOwnProperty()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you check the type of a variable in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["typeof", "type()", "checkType()", "varType()"],
        "answer": "typeof",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What will be the result of '5' == 5?",
        "options": ["true", "false", "undefined", "NaN"],
        "answer": "true",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to remove all elements from an array?",
        "options": ["clear()", "splice()", "pop()", "shift()"],
        "answer": "splice()",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operator is used to compare both value and type in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["==", "===", "=", "!="],
        "answer": "===",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'split()' method do in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
          "Splits a string into an array of substrings",
          "Merges an array into a string",
          "Compares two strings",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Splits a string into an array of substrings",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of '5' + 5 in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["10", "55", "Error", "undefined"],
        "answer": "55",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of [] + [] in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["[1, 2, 3]", "[5, 2, 3]", "1,23,4", "''"],
        "answer": "''",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of 5 + '5' in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["55", "10", "55 is NaN", "Error"],
        "answer": "55",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to check if a string contains a specific substring?",
        "options": ["includes()", "contains()", "find()", "search()"],
        "answer": "includes()",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'map()' method in JavaScript?",
        "options": [
          "To create a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element",
          "To sort an array",
          "To check if an element exists",
          "To remove elements from an array"
        ],
        "answer": "To create a new array with the results of calling a provided function on every element",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following code: console.log(0 == '0')?",
        "options": ["true", "false", "undefined", "NaN"],
        "answer": "true",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which method is used to check if a variable is an array?",
        "options": [
          "Array.isArray()",
          "instanceof Array",
          "isArray()",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "Array.isArray()",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of the expression {} + []?",
        "options": ["[object Object]", "[object Object][]", "{}", "[]"],
        "answer": "[object Object][]",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these is the correct way to handle errors in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["try/catch", "throw", "catch/throw", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of the following expression: NaN === NaN?",
        "options": ["true", "false", "undefined", "Error"],
        "answer": "false",
        "mode": "hard"
      }
    ],
    "indiaHistory": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the first Emperor of the Maurya Dynasty?",
        "options": ["Chandragupta Maurya", "Ashoka", "Bindusara", "Kautilya"],
        "answer": "Chandragupta Maurya",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the founder of the Mughal Empire?",
        "options": ["Akbar", "Babur", "Shah Jahan", "Aurangzeb"],
        "answer": "Babur",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first female ruler of India?",
        "options": [
          "Rani Lakshmi Bai",
          "Razia Sultana",
          "Indira Gandhi",
          "Sarojini Naidu"
        ],
        "answer": "Razia Sultana",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote the Indian national song 'Vande Mataram'?",
        "options": [
          "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay",
          "Rabindranath Tagore",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Satyendranath Tagore"
        ],
        "answer": "Bankim Chandra Chattopadhyay",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who led the Salt March in 1930?",
        "options": [
          "Mahatma Gandhi",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose"
        ],
        "answer": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the last Governor-General of independent India?",
        "options": [
          "Lord Mountbatten",
          "C. Rajagopalachari",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Lal Bahadur Shastri"
        ],
        "answer": "C. Rajagopalachari",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "When was the Indian Independence Act passed?",
        "options": ["1947", "1950", "1942", "1930"],
        "answer": "1947",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first President of India?",
        "options": [
          "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
          "Dr. Sarvepalli Radhakrishnan",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Dr. Zakir Husain"
        ],
        "answer": "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Father of the Nation' in India?",
        "options": [
          "Mahatma Gandhi",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "B.R. Ambedkar",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose"
        ],
        "answer": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Indian freedom fighter was known as 'Netaji'?",
        "options": [
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Chandra Shekhar Azad",
          "Bhagat Singh",
          "Lala Lajpat Rai"
        ],
        "answer": "Subhas Chandra Bose",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the last ruler of the Gupta Empire?",
        "options": [
          "Skandagupta",
          "Chandragupta I",
          "Chandragupta II",
          "Vikramaditya"
        ],
        "answer": "Skandagupta",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which battle marked the beginning of the British Empire in India?",
        "options": [
          "Battle of Plassey",
          "Battle of Panipat",
          "Battle of Buxar",
          "Battle of Haldighati"
        ],
        "answer": "Battle of Plassey",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first woman Prime Minister of India?",
        "options": [
          "Indira Gandhi",
          "Sarojini Naidu",
          "Rani Lakshmi Bai",
          "Sucheta Kriplani"
        ],
        "answer": "Indira Gandhi",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Indian leader is known for his role in the Champaran Satyagraha?",
        "options": [
          "Mahatma Gandhi",
          "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Lal Bahadur Shastri"
        ],
        "answer": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following was the first war of Indian Independence?",
        "options": [
          "First War of Indian Independence (1857)",
          "Battle of Panipat",
          "Battle of Plassey",
          "Sepoy Mutiny"
        ],
        "answer": "First War of Indian Independence (1857)",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Indian ruler is known for spreading Buddhism across Asia?",
        "options": ["Ashoka", "Chandragupta Maurya", "Harsha", "Samudragupta"],
        "answer": "Ashoka",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which movement did Gandhiji launch in 1942?",
        "options": [
          "Quit India Movement",
          "Non-Cooperation Movement",
          "Civil Disobedience Movement",
          "Salt March"
        ],
        "answer": "Quit India Movement",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first Sikh Guru?",
        "options": [
          "Guru Nanak",
          "Guru Gobind Singh",
          "Guru Arjan",
          "Guru Tegh Bahadur"
        ],
        "answer": "Guru Nanak",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first Indian to win the Nobel Prize?",
        "options": [
          "Rabindranath Tagore",
          "C. V. Raman",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Homi J. Bhabha"
        ],
        "answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first woman to be awarded the Bharat Ratna?",
        "options": [
          "Indira Gandhi",
          "Sarojini Naidu",
          "Mother Teresa",
          "Lata Mangeshkar"
        ],
        "answer": "Indira Gandhi",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which was the last Indian dynasty before British rule?",
        "options": ["Maratha", "Mughal", "Gupta", "Maurya"],
        "answer": "Maratha",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the architect of the Indian Constitution?",
        "options": [
          "Dr. B.R. Ambedkar",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Mahatma Gandhi"
        ],
        "answer": "Dr. B.R. Ambedkar",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote the famous book 'Discovery of India'?",
        "options": [
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Mahatma Gandhi",
          "C. Rajagopalachari"
        ],
        "answer": "Jawaharlal Nehru",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Indian leader gave the famous speech 'Give me blood and I will give you freedom'?",
        "options": [
          "Subhas Chandra Bose",
          "Bhagat Singh",
          "Lala Lajpat Rai",
          "Chandra Shekhar Azad"
        ],
        "answer": "Subhas Chandra Bose",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which empire's capital was 'Pataliputra'?",
        "options": [
          "Maurya Empire",
          "Gupta Empire",
          "Chola Empire",
          "Mughal Empire"
        ],
        "answer": "Maurya Empire",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first Muslim ruler of India?",
        "options": [
          "Qutb-ud-din Aibak",
          "Babar",
          "Muhammad Ghori",
          "Iltutmish"
        ],
        "answer": "Qutb-ud-din Aibak",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which famous battle was fought between the Marathas and the Mughals in 1707?",
        "options": [
          "Battle of Panipat",
          "Battle of Plassey",
          "Battle of Haldighati",
          "Battle of Karnal"
        ],
        "answer": "Battle of Panipat",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which famous Indian leader was known as the 'Iron Man of India'?",
        "options": [
          "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
          "Jawaharlal Nehru",
          "Lal Bahadur Shastri",
          "Subhas Chandra Bose"
        ],
        "answer": "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first European to land in India?",
        "options": [
          "Vasco da Gama",
          "Christopher Columbus",
          "Marco Polo",
          "Ferdinand Magellan"
        ],
        "answer": "Vasco da Gama",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the last Mughal emperor of India?",
        "options": ["Bahadur Shah Zafar", "Aurangzeb", "Akbar", "Shah Jahan"],
        "answer": "Bahadur Shah Zafar",
        "mode": "hard"
      }
    ],
    "geography": [
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of India?",
        "options": ["Mumbai", "Delhi", "Bangalore", "Chennai"],
        "answer": "Delhi",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which river is known as the 'Ganga of the South'?",
        "options": ["Yamuna", "Godavari", "Kaveri", "Krishna"],
        "answer": "Kaveri",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of France?",
        "options": ["Paris", "Berlin", "London", "Madrid"],
        "answer": "Paris",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the longest river in the world?",
        "options": ["Yangtze", "Amazon", "Nile", "Ganges"],
        "answer": "Nile",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest country in the world by area?",
        "options": ["USA", "Canada", "China", "Russia"],
        "answer": "Russia",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the largest desert in the world?",
        "options": ["Sahara", "Gobi", "Karakum", "Atacama"],
        "answer": "Sahara",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the tallest mountain in the world?",
        "options": ["Mount Everest", "K2", "Mount Kilimanjaro", "Kanchenjunga"],
        "answer": "Mount Everest",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ocean is the largest?",
        "options": [
          "Atlantic Ocean",
          "Indian Ocean",
          "Arctic Ocean",
          "Pacific Ocean"
        ],
        "answer": "Pacific Ocean",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which city is known as the 'City of Love'?",
        "options": ["Paris", "Rome", "Venice", "New York"],
        "answer": "Paris",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the national flower of India?",
        "options": ["Rose", "Lotus", "Tulip", "Sunflower"],
        "answer": "Lotus",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country has the most number of official languages?",
        "options": ["India", "Switzerland", "Canada", "South Africa"],
        "answer": "India",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country is known as the 'Land of the Rising Sun'?",
        "options": ["South Korea", "Japan", "Thailand", "China"],
        "answer": "Japan",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest island in the world?",
        "options": ["Greenland", "Australia", "Borneo", "New Guinea"],
        "answer": "Greenland",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the capital city of Australia?",
        "options": ["Sydney", "Melbourne", "Canberra", "Brisbane"],
        "answer": "Canberra",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which city is known as the 'Big Apple'?",
        "options": ["Los Angeles", "Chicago", "New York", "Miami"],
        "answer": "New York",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which river is known as the 'Amazon of India'?",
        "options": ["Godavari", "Yamuna", "Narmada", "Mahanadi"],
        "answer": "Godavari",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country is known as the 'Land of Midnight Sun'?",
        "options": ["Norway", "Finland", "Sweden", "Iceland"],
        "answer": "Norway",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country has the most pyramids?",
        "options": ["Egypt", "Mexico", "Sudan", "China"],
        "answer": "Sudan",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of Japan?",
        "options": ["Tokyo", "Osaka", "Kyoto", "Hiroshima"],
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest state in India by area?",
        "options": [
          "Uttar Pradesh",
          "Rajasthan",
          "Madhya Pradesh",
          "Maharashtra"
        ],
        "answer": "Rajasthan",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which river forms the boundary between India and Bangladesh?",
        "options": ["Ganges", "Brahmaputra", "Teesta", "Yamuna"],
        "answer": "Teesta",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the highest point in Africa?",
        "options": [
          "Mount Everest",
          "Mount Kilimanjaro",
          "Mount Kenya",
          "Mount Atlas"
        ],
        "answer": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the deepest lake in the world?",
        "options": [
          "Lake Baikal",
          "Caspian Sea",
          "Lake Superior",
          "Lake Tanganyika"
        ],
        "answer": "Lake Baikal",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the longest mountain range in the world?",
        "options": ["Andes", "Rockies", "Himalayas", "Alps"],
        "answer": "Andes",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the capital of Bhutan?",
        "options": ["Thimphu", "Kathmandu", "Dhaka", "Colombo"],
        "answer": "Thimphu",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country has the longest coastline in the world?",
        "options": ["Canada", "Russia", "USA", "Australia"],
        "answer": "Canada",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the largest archipelago in the world?",
        "options": ["Indonesia", "Philippines", "Maldives", "Canada"],
        "answer": "Indonesia",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which city is known as the 'City of Canals'?",
        "options": ["Amsterdam", "Venice", "Dubai", "Copenhagen"],
        "answer": "Venice",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which desert is located in northern China and southern Mongolia?",
        "options": ["Karakum", "Gobi", "Kalahari", "Atacama"],
        "answer": "Gobi",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the most populous city in the world?",
        "options": ["New York", "Shanghai", "Tokyo", "Delhi"],
        "answer": "Tokyo",
        "mode": "hard"
      }
    ],
    "music": [
      {
        "question": "Who sang the song 'Tum Hi Ho' from the movie Aashiqui 2?",
        "options": [
          "Arijit Singh",
          "Atif Aslam",
          "Sonu Nigam",
          "Shreya Ghoshal"
        ],
        "answer": "Arijit Singh",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which musical instrument is known as the 'king of Indian instruments'?",
        "options": ["Veena", "Sitar", "Tabla", "Sarod"],
        "answer": "Veena",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is associated with the famous musician Ravi Shankar?",
        "options": ["Sitar", "Tabla", "Flute", "Sarod"],
        "answer": "Sitar",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary instrument used in Hindustani classical music?",
        "options": ["Tabla", "Guitar", "Sitar", "Piano"],
        "answer": "Tabla",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these songs was sung by Lata Mangeshkar?",
        "options": [
          "Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya",
          "Madhuban Mein Radhika",
          "Dil Dhadakne Do",
          "Tum Jo Aaye"
        ],
        "answer": "Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is typically played with two sticks in Indian classical music?",
        "options": ["Tabla", "Dholak", "Bansuri", "Sitar"],
        "answer": "Tabla",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the composer of the song 'Kal Ho Na Ho'?",
        "options": [
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
          "Vishal-Shekhar",
          "S. D. Burman"
        ],
        "answer": "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the legendary singer of the song 'Aaj Phir Jeene Ki Tamanna Hai'?",
        "options": [
          "Lata Mangeshkar",
          "Mohammad Rafi",
          "Kishore Kumar",
          "Mukesh"
        ],
        "answer": "Lata Mangeshkar",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is used in the famous Bollywood song 'Tum Hi Ho'?",
        "options": ["Guitar", "Tabla", "Flute", "Piano"],
        "answer": "Piano",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these instruments is a string instrument used in Indian classical music?",
        "options": ["Sitar", "Tabla", "Bansuri", "Dholak"],
        "answer": "Sitar",
        "mode": "easy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the music director of the movie 'Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge'?",
        "options": [
          "Jatin-Lalit",
          "Nadeem-Shravan",
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy"
        ],
        "answer": "Jatin-Lalit",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which musical instrument is used to produce a continuous sound in Indian classical music?",
        "options": ["Harmonium", "Sitar", "Tabla", "Bansuri"],
        "answer": "Harmonium",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these singers is known as the 'Voice of India'?",
        "options": [
          "Mohammad Rafi",
          "Lata Mangeshkar",
          "Kishore Kumar",
          "Mukesh"
        ],
        "answer": "Kishore Kumar",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is considered the 'Queen of Indian Instruments'?",
        "options": ["Veena", "Tabla", "Sitar", "Sarod"],
        "answer": "Veena",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who composed the famous Bollywood song 'Tujh Mein Rab Dikhta Hai'?",
        "options": [
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Vishal-Shekhar",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
          "Pritam"
        ],
        "answer": "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main difference between the Sarod and Sitar?",
        "options": [
          "Sarod has more strings",
          "Sitar is played with fingers",
          "Sarod is played with a pick",
          "Sarod has no frets"
        ],
        "answer": "Sarod is played with a pick",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which famous singer is known for the song 'Chaiyya Chaiyya'?",
        "options": [
          "Udit Narayan",
          "Arijit Singh",
          "Kailasa Kher",
          "Sukhwinder Singh"
        ],
        "answer": "Sukhwinder Singh",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the composer for the movie 'Lagaan'?",
        "options": [
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Nadeem-Shravan",
          "Vishal-Shekhar",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy"
        ],
        "answer": "A. R. Rahman",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is most commonly associated with playing classical music in India?",
        "options": ["Veena", "Tabla", "Guitar", "Sitar"],
        "answer": "Sitar",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these instruments is used in traditional Bengali folk music?",
        "options": ["Ektara", "Tabla", "Harmonium", "Violin"],
        "answer": "Ektara",
        "mode": "medium"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which instrument is known for being used in both Western and Indian classical music, having four strings and played with a bow?",
        "options": ["Violin", "Sarod", "Flute", "Guitar"],
        "answer": "Violin",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who sang the song 'Ae Mere Humsafar' from the movie 'Baazigar'?",
        "options": [
          "Kishore Kumar",
          "Sonu Nigam",
          "Arijit Singh",
          "Udit Narayan"
        ],
        "answer": "Udit Narayan",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which music director composed the soundtrack for the movie 'Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna'?",
        "options": [
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
          "Pritam",
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Vishal-Shekhar"
        ],
        "answer": "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which classical Indian instrument is said to have 22 strings?",
        "options": ["Sitar", "Veena", "Sarod", "Tanpura"],
        "answer": "Sitar",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Mozart of Madras'?",
        "options": [
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Ilaiyaraaja",
          "Vishal-Shekhar",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy"
        ],
        "answer": "A. R. Rahman",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these songs was composed by the famous music director R.D. Burman?",
        "options": [
          "Pyaar Ka Toh Hai",
          "Mera Naam Chin Chin Chu",
          "Chura Liya Hai Tumne",
          "Ae Mere Humsafar"
        ],
        "answer": "Chura Liya Hai Tumne",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following Indian musicians is famous for playing the Sarod?",
        "options": [
          "Ravi Shankar",
          "Zakir Hussain",
          "Ustad Amjad Ali Khan",
          "Anoushka Shankar"
        ],
        "answer": "Ustad Amjad Ali Khan",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which musical instrument is played by striking it with a stick, commonly used in Indian temples?",
        "options": ["Ghungroo", "Dholak", "Pakhawaj", "Tabla"],
        "answer": "Pakhawaj",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who composed the music for the song 'Agar Tum Saath Ho' from 'Tamasha'?",
        "options": [
          "A. R. Rahman",
          "Pritam",
          "Shankar-Ehsaan-Loy",
          "Vishal-Shekhar"
        ],
        "answer": "A. R. Rahman",
        "mode": "hard"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these songs was sung by Kishore Kumar?",
        "options": [
          "Chalte Chalte",
          "Pyaar Kiya To Darna Kya",
          "Mera Naam Chin Chin Chu",
          "Ek Ladki Ko Dekha"
        ],
        "answer": "Mera Naam Chin Chin Chu",
        "mode": "hard"
      }
    ]
  }
]
